http://www.catalogs.com/privacy.asp

We at Catalogs.com are firmly committed to protecting your
privacy.  We respect your privacy, and we want you to feel comfortable
using our website. Therefore, we are providing you with this privacy
policy so you can better understand our commitment to how your personal
information will be secured and handled.  We are committed to collecting,
maintaining, and securing your personal information in strict accordance
with the principles described in this policy.
Personal Information
By viewing our website, we do not collect any personal information
about you.  Should you actively request to receive a catalog, newsletter, savings certificate or other information
from our website, we will ask that you voluntarily provide us with certain information about yourself (collectively,
your personal information). Your personal information is comprised of the information that you voluntarily fill
in on our order form and your Internet Protocol (IP) address
How Do You Use My Personal Information?
Except as stated below, we DO NOT share your personal information nor use it for list rental purposes.
When you order a catalog, newsletter, savings certificate or other information through our website, your personal
information is provided only to the company(s) from which you ordered.
This helps ensure that your order
is processed correctly and timely delivered.
On occasion, we may engage third parties to perform certain functions on our behalf.
Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, removing repetitive information from the customer list,
analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, and providing customer service. These third parties have
access to your personal information to the extent necessary to permit them to do their jobs, however,
they may not use it for other purposes.
We also may disclose your personal information if we are required to do so by law and we believe in good
faith that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend
our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website; or (4) protect the
personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide
false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any
investigation into your actions).
In addition, we may use the information we obtain from our customers in the aggregate to determine
our website users' demographics and preferences. By doing so, we are able to deliver targeted advertisements
on our website which you may find to be helpful and informative.
Also, in the unlikely event that part or
all of Catalogs.com assets are acquired, personal information may be one of the transferred assets.
Except as stated above, we DO NOT share your personal information with any other parties.
Opting - In at Catalogs.com
When you order a catalog, newsletter, savings certificate or other information through our website, you will also be opted-in to receive email updates and special savings offers from Catalogs.com.
Opting -Out
Our email updates provide you with the opportunity to decline or opt-out of receiving information on new products,
services, special offers and upcoming events from Catalogs.com.
How Do I Update My Personal Information?
In order to make sure that you receive the full benefit of our website, you should make sure that we
have the most up-to-date information about you. Please remember that we will not remind you to update your
information, and it is your responsibility to make sure that we have your correct information.
If you want to update your account information at Catalogs.com, you may re-enter or modify your personal
information by completing a new order form.
Internet Privacy
In order to provide better service, we may use cookies.
A cookie is a small amount of data which our
website stores on your computer, and which we can later retrieve. The cookie cannot be read by a site other than ours.
We use cookies for administrative purposes only; for example, to store your preferences for certain kinds of information.
No cookie will contain information that will allow anyone to contact you via telephone, e-mail, or any other means.
You can monitor our use of cookies on your computer by setting your Web browser to inform you when cookies are set, or
you can prevent the cookies from being set entirely. The help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how
to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or
how to disable cookies altogether. Please understand that if you disable the use of cookies on your computer, you may be
unable to access certain portions or services of our website. Catalogs.com also may use third parties to display
advertisements and track leads and/or sales from our website. These ads and/or tracking functions may use cookies.
Catalogs.com does not control these cookies, and they are not subject to Catalogs.com's privacy policy.
Keeping Things Safe
We want you to feel secure when using our website.
To that end, we work with catalog companies and
other merchants that have been in business for many years and have a proven track record of reliability.
We also take reasonable steps to protect our servers and data centers in order to prevent the loss, misuse and
alteration of any personal information under our control.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
Catalogs.com is a website directed to the general public. Catalogs.com does not knowingly offer catalogs
or services to children, nor does Catalogs.com knowingly request information from children. If you are under 18,
you should use our website only with the involvement and supervision of a parent or adult guardian.
We reserve the right to cancel, without prior notice to you, any orders for catalogs or services ordered by
you if we know, or have reason to believe, you are not over the age of 18.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
As our customers' needs change, we may find it necessary to amend or revise this Privacy Policy.
Any such revisions or additions will be posted on this page. Please re-visit this page from time to
time to make sure that you are aware of any additions or revisions to this policy. If you have any
concern about privacy at Catalogs.com, we want you to tell us about it.
Drop us an email at
info@catalogs.com,
and we will try to get your questions answered.
Get FREE SHIPPING from 100s of Stores
Sign up for exclusive email offers.
Have a Catalog?
For a Limited Time, We are waving our Listing Fee!!
Want One?
Learn about our Patented Dynalog Technology
And for a limited time, get free lifetime Listing!
Apply to have your Company listed.
© 1997-2020 Catalogs.com
